SUMMARY

I am a web developer with a background in food service retail leadership. I'm excited to help develop meaningful technologies which impact and improve people's lives. Specializing in Ruby on Rails, Javascript, HTML5, and CSS, my goal is to master many frameworks so that I can be a highly independent developer. I have years of leadership experience in large organizations. This has taught me how to prioritize and juggle many tasks, lead and inspire team members, celebrate diverse personalities, meet deadlines with a sense of urgency, be a team player, and maintain a professional environment. I thrive in a client facing environment.

If you would like to contact me about joining your team or other opportunities you may reach me at:

justincadburywong@gmail.com

CONTACT

■ justincadburywong@gmail.com

iustincadburywong.github.io

415-845-9551

in /in/justin-cadbury-wong

iustincadburywong

EDUCATION

Dev Bootcamp

Dev Bootcamp is a 19-week intensive training program for aspiring web developers, specializing in Ruby, Rails, HTML5, CSS, Test Driven Development, Object-Oriented Javascript (AJAX, JQuery), Git and Source Control, Heroku ad Agile Development. The first 9 weeks of the curriculum are remote, while the second 9 weeks are an immersive inclass experience. The program also addresses intra- and interpersonal strategies to foster optimal learning and teamwork environments.

College of Marin AA Liberal Arts 2007

The College of Marin is an accredited institution with courses in

EMPLOYMENT

Recent Dev Bootcamp Graduate

Junior Software Developer

Aug 2016 to Current

I recently graduated from Dev Bootcamp and am now looking for my first job as a junior developer, whether that be via apprenticeship, internship, or full time position. A former retail team leader, I am passionate about developing and curating my team around the focus of the job, and working for a company with a strong mission and purpose

Dev Bootcamp Student

Web Developer

May 2016 to Aug 2016

Dev Bootcamp is a 19-week intensive training program for aspiring web developers, specializing in Ruby, Rails, HTML5, CSS, Test Driven Development, Object-Oriented Javascript (AJAX, JQuery), Git and Source Control, Heroku ad Agile Development. The first 9 weeks of the curriculum are remote, while the second 9 weeks are an immersive in-class experience. The program also addresses intra- and interpersonal strategies to foster optimal learning and teamwork environments.

Whole Foods Market

Associate Team Leader

2007 to 2016

In my role, I was responsible for recruiting, hiring, training, motivating, and holding accountable all of the 40+ team members with their daily duties. I was also charged with delegating tasks and responsibilities to our supervisor group, who conducted the day to day operations of the store. I also coordinated with my store team leader to set and achieve the highest standards in retail execution, and help drive customer service while ensuring the team has total store awareness. As a team player, I was also an integral contributor towards maximizing productivity and efficiency through proper scheduling, helping to achieve required financial targets, maintaining a safe, clean and well-organized working and shopping environment, and complying with all regulatory rules and regulations including HACCP, OSHA, Dept. of Labor, Weights and Measures and local food and sanitation laws.

PROJECTS

Naebrz Aug 2016 to Current

Naebrz is a way to create and monitor events with your friends and neighbors(naebrz). Written in Ruby on Sinatra.

https://github.com/justincadburywong/Naebrz-App

Rooki Aug 2016 to Current

Rooki is an OpenCV API that digests sequential pictures of chess games to generate notations for review. Written in Python on Django. Front end written in React Native. https://github.com/justincadburywong/Rooki-OpenCV-App

Inspire Sep 2016 to Current

Inspire is a rails app utilizing the IBM Watson API to run sentiment analysis on a user's quote to determine how inspiring it is. Written in Ruby on Rails.

https://github.com/justincadburywong/Inspire

TinyPay Oct 2016 to Current

TinyPay is an SMS based payment system using the MasterCard SendP2P payment API. Written in Ruby on Rails.

https://github.com/justincadburywong/tinypay-1

SKILLS

Object Oriented Design, Ruby, JavaScript, HTML5, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), ActiveRecord, Heroku, SQLite, PostgreSQL, Git, RSpec, JavaScript, Sinatra, Team Management, Leadership, Public Speaking, Customer Service